

# JESSE ROSE

SENIOR PRODUCT PERSON



#### PROFILE

Consumer-focused product leader with 8+ years of experience helping early-stage companies scale. I believe that brand and product are powerful tools that should work in concert to solve real problems and win over users.

Current problem: where should you eat next?

+1 978 210 1446

jesse.rose13@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/jesserose/

New York, New York

# EDUCATION

# Bachelor of Business Administration

The George Washington University School of Business 2007 - 2011

# SKILLS & INTERESTS

Product Strategy Design Thinking

Team Building Recruiting & Hiring

Strategic Planning Agile Methodologies

Brand Development Data & Analytics

Soccer Magic My dog, Rex

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Head of Product

2016 - 2019

Product Management & Product Design

### The Infatuation

- Joined as first technical hire and ninth full-time hire. Grew the product and engineering team to 12 including our CTO, engineers, product designers, and product managers.
- Lead a team of product managers and product designers across web, iOS, Android, email, and SMS (text message) resulting in more than 600% increase in monthly active users (MAUs).
- Craft, socialize, prioritize, and drive the vision for all of The Infatuation's product strategy.
- Establish and evolve our product development process to define KPIs, incorporate both quantitative and qualitative baselines, introduce in-person user testing and prototyping practice, and iterate for desired results.
- Acted as a key stakeholder during investor pitch and duediligence process, culminating in raising \$30+ MM in funding.
- Launched new revenue-generating products like subscriptions and a content API. Support the partnerships team in pitching and implementation with partners.
- Operate happily wearing many hats, with a no-job-too-small mentality. Approach new challenges and problems with a practical but thorough problem-solving approach. When there isn't a subject-matter expert in house, I work to become one.

# Zagat

- Collaborated in crafting our acquisition proposal of Zagat from Google. Pitched to Google management.
- •Led product vision definition process, MVP (minimum viable product) strategy, and rollout planning for a complete platform reset.
- Act as a steering committee member for brand re-introduction rollout, community building efforts, and book relaunch.

# Senior Product Manager

2014 - 2016

Big Human

• Planned, branded, designed, and built digital products across various industries such as Urban Dictionary, Gemini, Helix Sleep, and The Flatiron School.

# Digital Producer

2012 - 2013

Droga5

Associate Digital Producer 2011 - 2012 Code & Theory